{
    "subject": "resource/Paula_Cole",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Cole, Paula",
    "human_readable": "The name of Paula Cole is Cole, Paula.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9679166078567505,
            "question": "What is the full name of Paula Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9378281235694885,
            "question": "What is Paula Cole's last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9326732754707336,
            "question": "Is Paula Cole's name listed in the format 'Last Name, First Name'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9157289266586304,
            "question": "What is Paula Cole's first name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8126343488693237,
            "question": "How many words are in Paula Cole's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8064092993736267,
            "question": "Could you re-write Paula Cole's name with her first name coming first?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7588034272193909,
            "question": "Is 'Cole' a common last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7545867562294006,
            "question": "What is the order of Paula Cole's first and last names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5728619694709778,
            "question": "If you were to address Paula Cole formally, what would you say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5313107967376709,
            "question": "Is 'Paula' a common first name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Paula Cole is Cole, Paula.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9053_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to address Paula Cole formally, what would you say?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9053_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the order of Paula Cole's first and last names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9053_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Cole' a common last name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9053_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9053_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided that states \"Paula Cole (born April 5, 1968) is an American singer-songwriter.\" This confirms that her name is indeed Cole, Paula."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}